<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--Historic places Names-->
    <string-array name="h_places">
        <item>Uxbridge Wood</item>
        <item>St Margarets Church</item>
        <item>St Georges Chapel</item>
        <item>Chiltern Open Air Museum</item>
        <item>Runnymede National Trust</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Historic places descriptions-->
    <string-array name="h_places_descriptions">
        <item>Uxbridge Woods Trust was established in 1997 as a charity.
        Its aims are to protect the ecological environment of Uxbridge Woods
        and to encourage greater access by the public through education,
        monitoring and surveying.
        </item>
        <item>
            We seek to be a loving and welcoming
            community inspired by the example of Jesus,
            influenced by the vibrant life of God’s Spirit and
            making a positive contribution to our town
        </item>
        <item>
            To the Glory of God, and in grateful commemoration of His servants,
            Thomas Cranmer, Nicholas Ridley, Hugh Latimer, Prelates of the Church of England,
            who near this spot yielded their bodies to be burned, bearing witness to the sacred
            truths which they had affirmed and maintained against the errors of the Church of Rome,
            and rejoicing that to them it was given not only to believe in Christ, but also to suffer
            for His sake; this monument was erected by public subscription in the year of our Lord God.
        </item>
        <item>
            By the 1850s the population of both Hillingdon and Uxbridge
            was beginning to rise. With new housing being built between the
            two centres the then Vicar of Hillingdon, the Rev Richard Croft (1856–69)
            gained permission to build a new church in the area, sometimes referred to
            as Hillingdon West.
        </item>
        <item>
            The dedication of the lime tree seat on the Village Green
            in memory of long-standing volunteer Gladys Taaffe
            Founded in 1976 to rescue threatened historic buildings
            Chiltern Open Air Museum was founded in 1976 with the aim of
            rescuing threatened buildings.  More than thirty historic building have
            now been saved and rebuilt at the site, and there are more in store.
            The Museum only accepts buildings that would otherwise be demolished.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Historic sites locations-->
    <string-array name="h_place_location">
        <item>22 Aldridge Avenue, Eastcote, Ruislip, Middlesex HA4 9JU</item>
        <item>Windsor Street, Uxbridge UB8 1AB, England</item>
        <item>The Lynch | Opposite Capital Court, Uxbridge UB8 1AB, England</item>
        <item>Castle Hill, Windsor, England</item>
        <item>Newland Park Gorelands Lane, Chalfont St. Giles HP8 4AB, England</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Historic sites pictures-->
    <string-array name="h_places_images">
        <item>@drawable/uxbridge_wood</item>
        <item>@drawable/st_margaret_s_church</item>
        <item>@drawable/st_george</item>
        <item>@drawable/chiltern_open_air_museum</item>
        <item>@drawable/runnymede</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
